 <?xml version="1.0"?>
 <Rooms>
	<RespawnRoomID>1000</RespawnRoomID>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>2000</ID>
		<Name>Path  </Name>
		<Description>other world.</Description>
		<WorldID>world2</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>1000</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>1000</ID>
		<Name>Enveloped in gloom  </Name>
		<Description>The trees overhang the path like dark souls waiting upon ill luck to
bring them their next victim. Long trailers of moss hang from the
branches distorting their already bent and twisted forms. The bushes
along the trail seem to reach towards you as you wend your way through.
Looking southward, the trail can be seen ending in a dark cave entrance.</Description>
		<WorldID>local</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>1001</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>2000</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	<Room>
		<ID>1001</ID>
		<Name>A dark cave </Name>
		<Description>Covered in a slimy sweat, those rough hewn walls close in about you like
a wet blanket.  Rotting garbage litters the ground, adding a distinct odor
to the cave.  Holding your nose against the smell and decay, you wonder if
you should explore deeper.</Description>
		<WorldID>local</WorldID>
		<Monster>Rabbit</Monster>
		<Monster>Deer</Monster>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>	
			<RoomID>1000</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>e</Direction>
			<RoomID>1002</RoomID>
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>sw</Direction>
			<RoomID>1006</RoomID>
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	<Room>
		<ID>1002</ID>
		<Name>A dank passage </Name>
		<Description>Dank, putrid air hangs heavily along this passage.  Offal and waste splatter
the walls in in a random patterning of decay and abandon.  Whoever lives here
has no respect for the homes or themselves.
Exits: north east south west </Description>
		<WorldID>local</WorldID>
		<Monster>Deer</Monster>
		<Monster>Skeleton</Monster>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>w</Direction>
			<RoomID>1001</RoomID>
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>e</Direction>
			<RoomID>1005</RoomID>
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>1003</RoomID>
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>1004</RoomID>
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	<Room>
		<ID>1003</ID>
		<Name>Dust and decay </Name>
		<Description>A cloud of dust rises at your entrance, obscuring the room momentarily,
and sending you into a coughing fit. Old, ratty piles of furs dot the
floor of this home. The layers of dust show that this home has not been
used in quite some time.</Description>
		<WorldID>local</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>1002</RoomID>
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	<Room>
		<ID>1004</ID>
		<Name>A tiny home</Name>
		<Description>Tiny and cramped, this is home to several individuals. At least a
dozen rotting piles of furs line the floor, leaving little room to
maneuver. A small pile of rotting food takes up the southeast corner.</Description>
		<WorldID>local</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>1002</RoomID>
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	<Room>
		<ID>1005</ID>
		<Name>A rancid pile </Name>
		<Description>A huge pile of offal and bones occupies almost this entire chamber.
Fumes and colorful gases can be seen rising up from this putrescense,
causing your eyes to water. A strange fungus grows along the walls
of this room.</Description>
		<WorldID>local</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>w</Direction>
			<RoomID>1002</RoomID>
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>1006</ID>
		<Name>A dank passage </Name>
		<Description>Dank, putrid air hangs heavily along this passage.  Offal and waste splatter
the walls in a random patterning of decay and abandon.  Whoever lives here
has no respect for their homes or themselves.</Description>
		<WorldID>local</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>ne</Direction>
			<RoomID>1001</RoomID>
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>1007</RoomID>
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>1008</RoomID>
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>1007</ID>
		<Name>A turn in the passageway </Name>
		<Description>The passage turns here, moving in to the west and south.  As with other 
sections of this tunnel, garbage lines the walls like the putrid remains
of some ghastly parade.</Description>
		<WorldID>local</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>1006</RoomID>
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>1009</RoomID>
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>w</Direction>
			<RoomID>1010</RoomID>
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>1008</ID>
		<Name>A home of bones </Name>
		<Description>Bones litter the floor here forming piles and heaps about the room.  Like
the forgotten castoffs of a child, these bones are the remains of many a
forgotten meal.  Like all other hobgoblin homes, this one has never been
cleaned.</Description>
		<WorldID>local</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>1006</RoomID>
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>1009</ID>
		<Name>An empty space  </Name>
		<Description>A layer of dust, inches thick, sheets the ground here.  Huge cobwebs cover
the corners, lending this room a more rounded look.  Judging by the amount
of dust and the state of decay amongst the bits and pieces of garbage, this
room has not seen use in quite some time.</Description>
		<WorldID>local</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>1007</RoomID>
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>1010</ID>
		<Name>The end of the tunnel</Name>
		<Description>The passageway comes to an end here. Three chambers can be seen leading
off to the north, south and west. The chamber to the west seems much 
larger than any others you have seen so far. The sound of grunts and
shuffling feet can be heard to the west.</Description>
		<WorldID>local</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>e</Direction>
			<RoomID>1007</RoomID>
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>1011</RoomID>
		</Exit>

		<Exit> 
			<Direction>w</Direction>
			<RoomID>1012</RoomID>
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>1011</ID>
		<Name>A foul spring</Name>
		<Description>A small pool of water rests along the northern wall of this small
chamber. The source of the water is a spring bubbling forth from
a crack in the north wall. Another crack in the floor seems to
siphon off the excess water. This seems to be the main source of
water for the hobgoblins.</Description>
		<WorldID>local</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>1010</RoomID>
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>1012</ID>
		<Name>The guard room</Name>
		<Description>Several rancid piles of fur dot the floor in this chamber.  Rusted pieces
of weaponry and rotting armor line the walls in a sad imitation of military
order.  Whatever chambers lie to the north are obviously important enough
to have warranted a guard chamber here.</Description>
		<WorldID>local</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>e</Direction>
			<RoomID>1010</RoomID>
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>1013</RoomID>
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>1013</ID>
		<Name>The chief guard</Name>
		<Description>Large slabs of granite have been haphazardly assembled into a huge desk
of sorts.  Several pieces of rusted weaponry occupy places of honour 
behind the desk.  A large, thick slab of granite forms a door to the north.</Description>
		<WorldID>local</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>1012</RoomID>
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>1014</RoomID>
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	<Room>
		<ID>1014</ID>
		<Name>The King's chamber</Name>
		<Description>Large, almost fresh hides and furs hang along the walls of this huge chamber.
As you look at them, there is barely a hint of rot about them.  A tall throne
of roughly cut granite stands at the end of the chamber.  Several torches 
along the walls give this chamber a brighter look than any other chamber you
have found. There is a large throne blocking the travel west.</Description>
		<WorldID>local</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>1013</RoomID>
		</Exit>
	</Room>
 </Rooms>
 