<!--
	All room descriptions taken from:
	http://www.realmsofdespair.com/
-->

<?xml version="1.0"?>
 <Rooms>
	<RespawnRoomID>2000</RespawnRoomID>	
	
	<Room>
		<ID>1000</ID>
		<Name>Enveloped in gloom</Name>
		<Description>The trees overhang the path like dark souls waiting upon ill luck to
bring them their next victim. Long trailers of moss hang from the
branches distorting their already bent and twisted forms. The bushes
along the trail seem to reach towards you as you wend your way through.
Looking southward, the trail can be seen ending in a dark cave entrance.</Description>
		<WorldID>world1</WorldID>
	</Room>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>2000</ID>
		<Name>Inside Darkwall, Southern Gate of Darkhaven</Name>
		<Description>You stand inside Darkwall, the southern gate of Darkhaven. Named after
its daily defense against the goblins and balrogs to the south, it is
literally an impenetrable wall.  To the north is the intersection of
Vertic Avenue and Law Avenue.</Description>
		<WorldID>world2</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>2001</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>1000</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>2001</ID>
		<Name>Intersection of Vertic Avenue and Law Avenue</Name>
		<Description>You stand at the intersection of Vertic Avenue and Law Avenue.  Gazing to
the south, you see the massive south gate of Darkhaven, known as Darkwall.
The cobbled roads of Vertic Avenue and Law Avenue lie in the four
cardinal directions.</Description>
		<WorldID>world2</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>2000</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>2002</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>2002</ID>
		<Name>The Vertic Avenue Crossroad</Name>
		<Description>While traversing the busy, cobbled streets of Darkhaven, you notice
a particularly dark alley to the west which citizens commonly avoid.
Grinning, you imagine the cloaked thief lurking in the shadows. Rising
up to the east are a number of tall trees, no doubt from the park upon
which the street was named. Vertic Avenue extends to the north and south.</Description>
		<WorldID>world2</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>2001</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>2003</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	
	<Room>
		<ID>2003</ID>
		<Name>Intersection of Vertic Avenue and Market Street</Name>
		<Description>You stand at the intersection of Vertic Avenue and Market Street.  The
intersection bustles with activity as citizens go about their business.
To the east and west runs Market Street, lined with the exotic shops of
Darkhaven, while Vertic Avenue lies to the north and south.</Description>
		<WorldID>world2</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>2002</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>2004</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>e</Direction>
			<RoomID>2006</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>2004</ID>
		<Name>Vertic Avenue</Name>
		<Description>This portion of Vertic Avenue is crowded by tents on both sides and littered
with discarded bits of paper and sacks from the shops. The dirt road was
recently extended as the markets of Darkhaven continue to grow and spread
across the southern end of town. To the south, dust and loud, haggling
voices drift in from the main intersection of the market.</Description>
		<WorldID>world2</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>2003</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>2005</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>2005</ID>
		<Name>Darkhaven Square</Name>
		<Description>You are standing within the expanse of the famous Darkhaven Square.
An immense stone statue of Duke Luther sits in the center of the square,
surrounded by fountains of shimmering crystal water.  Gardens and shrubbery
enhance the air of serenity and peace here in the center of the great city.
A plaque set into the base of the fountain attracts your eye.  Cobblestone
roads lead away in the four cardinal directions, while to the northeast
and northwest are forested paths.  The cathedral spires of Notre Dame
de Sioux rise with majesty above the treetops to the northwest.</Description>
		<WorldID>world2</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>2004</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	
	<Room>
		<ID>2006</ID>
		<Name>Market Street</Name>
		<Description>The cobbled road is buzzing with activity.  Eager shouts from numerous tents
and pavilions encourage potential customers to come inspect a shopkeeper's
wares.  To the north is the Food Market, while the tent to the south is
dedicated to repairing items.  Market Street stretches to the east and west.</Description>
		<WorldID>world2</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>w</Direction>
			<RoomID>2003</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>2007</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	<Room>
		<ID>2007</ID>
		<Name>The Solid Parry </Name>
		<Description>This shop's owner is a dedicated creator of armor and shields.  Having lost
her son to shabby equipment, she took up the job of putting protective suits
of mail together.  The Daring Attack is to the east.  An opening in the tent leads back out north onto Market Street.
There is a small sign here.</Description>
		<WorldID>world2</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>2006</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>e</Direction>
			<RoomID>2008</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>2008</ID>
		<Name>The Daring Attack</Name>
		<Description>Racks line the walls of this tent, each filled to the brim with weapons.
You grin evilly at the items of destruction, and try out a couple on the
practice dummies hung from the ceiling.  A counter in the center of the
room is where the keeper of this shop does business.  To the west is
the Solid Parry, while an opening in the tent to the north leads
back out onto Market Street.</Description>
		<WorldID>world2</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>w</Direction>
			<RoomID>2007</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>2009</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	
	<Room>
		<ID>2009</ID>
		<Name>Market Street</Name>
		<Description>You smile at the familiar sight of Market Street and its glorious pavilions.
The ring of sword on sword can be heard to the south, while the dairy is
situated to the north.  Market Street extends east and west.</Description>
		<WorldID>world2</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>2008</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>e</Direction>
			<RoomID>2006</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>n</Direction>
			<RoomID>2010</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	<Room>
		<ID>2010</ID>
		<Name>Matilda's Dairy Products</Name>
		<Description>This small shop smells strongly of cheese, as dozens of types of cheeses
have been laid out and labeled properly on several long shelves.  You notice
many bottles of milk, which Matilda considers to be more important than even
water, carefully stacked in the northeast corner.  To the west is the
Darkhaven Bakery, while Market Street lies to the south.</Description>
		<WorldID>world2</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>w</Direction>
			<RoomID>2011</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>2009</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
	</Room>
	<Room>
		<ID>2011</ID>
		<Name>The Darkhaven Bakery</Name>
		<Description>Upon entering the Darkhaven Bakery, you find yourself surrounded by citizens
of the marvelous city, each waiting in line for their daily bread.  Gazing
eastward, you see a farmer's shop which sells all forms of dairy products.
A butcher's shop also lies to the west, while an opening in the tent to
the south leads back out onto Market Street.</Description>
		<WorldID>world2</WorldID>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>s</Direction>
			<RoomID>2006</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
		<Exit> 
			<Direction>e</Direction>
			<RoomID>2010</RoomID>			
		</Exit>
	</Room>	
 </Rooms>
 